The kettle and the idol
Well, here we are at the fast ending.
It goes by so fast.
May I send an announcement from Ms. Tachibana?
Yes, you may. Thank you very much.
Iginari Tohokusan is currently on a nationwide tour called "Nationwide Never Lose Tour.
The tour finale will be held on Friday, May 19 and Saturday, May 20 at Line Cube Shibuya in Tokyo.
Please check the official website and Twitter for ticket information.
What do you think?
We are going to perform at the tour finale in Shibuya, Tokyo on Saturday and Sunday,
We are also performing a lot of new songs,
I hope we can surprise you with the final form of our tour here at Line Cube Shibuya.
The tour final here is the tour final, and the 20th is already sold out, isn't it?
That's right.
The 19th is still available, so please come and join us.
And now...
Tokyo Idol Festival 2023 will be held in Odaiba for three days from Friday, August 4 to Sunday, August 6,
Iginari Tohokusan will also perform at the festival.
And..,
And, Iginari Tohokusan will be performing at the end of the year 2023.
It will be held on Friday, December 29th at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall.
Please look forward to it.
What do you have in mind?
It's a big venue.
Yes, it is. I have only seen the Pacifico in pictures,
It is really big, isn't it?
It is huge.
I am a little nervous,
I am a little nervous, but this is the culmination of this year's event,
I want to spread out my body with a bang,
I want to spread my body out with a bang and connect with my feelings with a bang.
It's nice, isn't it?
I hope you will be able to join us in this live performance and convey your feelings with a bang.
And last but not least, please give us a few words.
This is a live performance that is broadcast every Monday night at 7 p.m. on Teresa Video,
Akira Kawakami's One-Person Loincloth Girl.
I, Karen Tachibana, am in charge of the 4th week.
The theme is the road to becoming a staff sample craftsman.
Thank you very much.
Now, to the end,
May I present you with a cup of tea, Mr. Yakacan?
Is that okay?
Today's tea is chilancha.
It is a green tea.
I hope you will enjoy it.
Bon appétit.
It's warm.
Delicious!
Is it good?
It tastes good!
Tastes good!
Delicious!
Comfortable!
Yes!
Amazing!
Wow, it smells great.
Well, do you usually drink tea?
I like tea a lot.
Oh, I see.
Yes, I do.
Now, let's finish up with the camera, shall we?
Well, if you could end on a cute note,
Yes.
Yes, that will be the end.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm not asking you to tighten it up.
I'm sorry.
My expression was a little strange, wasn't it?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much for watching the kettle and the idols today.
Tohoku-san will continue to do its best in Tohoku,
I would be very happy if you could come and visit us in Tohoku as well,
I am sure that Mr. Yoru will continue to do his best, and I will do my best as well,
Please look forward to our activities.
Thank you very much for your time today.
This is Karen Tachibana from Ujira, Michinoku of Stardust, Iginari Tohoku-san.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
This program is Mikan-san. Happy Birthday, Ms. Nana-san.
Karen's Jyunkyun Katsusan and SanKarei no Junkun Katsusan to San
Sent to you courtesy of Tomo-san
Thank you for all your support.